时间是肯定够的,因为我们是到,就中国的时间,北京时间9月16日的下午3点59分结束,还有一个月的时间,你可以去准备。
这次会有抽奖吗?你说MD啊?线上啊?没有诶。
等以后MD官方这个号粉丝多了的话,我就可以去问他们要一些奖品,比如说许可证啊之类的。
嗯,MD做了CBR,这次没有准备诶,以后下次吧。
因为我一般都是在MD里面叼的,MD出叼了之后我就直接在MD里面叼的。
还有一个,还有一个月的时间从头开始学啊,不要吧。
嗯,也来得及。
嗯,那我们现在就开始今天的这个视频。
呃,我本来想吐槽自己的,算了。
现在就开始今天的直播吧。
呃,接下来我会为大家播放一个我事先已经录制好的demo视频。
然后在这个视频播放的过程中,
我们会跟大家分享这个视频。
我们会为大家解释怎么样在MD里面去制作一套完整的中国风的一套猎人的服装。
嗯,首先我想吐槽一下就是,
嗯,官方设定这一次Crytec和Marvelous Designer合作的这个主题是猎杀对决里面的猎人的服装。
那猎杀对决它主要是有一个大前提的时间、时代一个前提的。
它是1800年到1900年。
嗯,19XX年之间的这段时间。
就是19世纪初到20世纪中左右的时间。
然后当时我们韩国这边跟我提这个主题之后,
我去着手进行了一个准备。
然后呢,在我查看了一些资料之后,
我发现1800年到1900年中国没有经常用枪。
我就,好吧,我只能凭借自己的一点,
就是猜测和想法还有官方给我的一些参考图去做呢这一次的主题。
对啊,就涉及到历史了。
然后当时唯一用枪的是1900年初的一些联军。
他们会用枪。
主要我们之前还是比较喜欢用冷兵器的。
而且1800年到1900年的那段时间,
嗯,中间还经历过比如说像马汉啊,
他们一些就是用弓啊之类的弓刀枪比较多。
然后像这种猎人用的枪其实还是比较少的。
对,火器就比较少。
然后猎杀对决因为它比较多,都是拿枪嘛。
所以我就主要参考了一些,
嗯,就是像我们近代的清朝的那样子的一个装扮。
对,我也做,找了比较多的参考,各种各样的参考。
首先还是就导入这个模特了。
导入模特之后呢,我就会在我们的系统里面找一套默认的服装给它穿上,重新安排。
这里也可能速度比较快。
大家要跟上。
然后呢,我就会参考压力图,去对它的一个尺寸进行一个更改。
包括对它的一个袖子的长度进行一个调整。
因为我们古代的小伙伴们,他们还是一般都穿着比较长的袖子。
然后在穿着完毕之后,我会对它的尺寸进行一些更细致的调整。
其实我对盗墓贼倒不是很了解了。
而且他们比较喜欢拿锄头吧。
然后就对它袖口的长度进行一些调整,让它看上去就比较顺眼一点吧。
总之就是不断地在测试,怎么样去让它有一个更好的效果。
然后大家可以看到袖子这里,我是把它的弧线改平了一点。
大家在做一些比较宽松的衣服的时候,袖子这个曲线一定要记得出来的平一点。
然后一定要有直角。
洛阳铲。
《丽莎对决》里面不可能用铲子的呀。
然后我就会基于它的一个压力图去看它有没有哪一些部分压力比较大。
我就会调整一下。
因为古人穿的衣服整体还是比较宽松的。
然后我在做这个衣服的过程中,我就不断在放周杰伦的霍元甲。
因为我实在想不到,就是清朝那个年代的人,他们平时穿衣服是什么样的。
然后我就把周董的那个霍元甲那个MV就拿出来。
然后一边看那个,就是听他那个霍霍霍霍霍霍霍霍霍。
然后一边在做这个衣服。
然后大家可以看到我之前把服装模特的表面间距降低了。
这样可以让最里层的衣服能贴近我们模特的皮肤。
因为默认的模特导进来的时候,它的表面间距是3嘛。
衣服就会看上去有点悬空。
接下去我就会用板片外线扩张工具,直接在我们的默认服装外面扩张出一个领子出来。
这样就不用再手动去绘制了。
然后就会用板片外线扩张工具直接在我们的默认服装外面扩张出一个领子出来。
然后当我们把这个领子缝合起来的时候呢,就会看到它的侧边有点不太贴合。
然后我就会去对它的侧边进行一个调整。
接下去就是做它的领子,是个圆弧形的那种领子。
这样啊,我倒不知道,因为我不怎么看盗墓的事情。
盗墓笔记这种我没怎么看,我才知道盗墓的人是要用手枪的。
那还挺符合这种想法的,可以去做一个。
我整体做的一个想法还是就是先做清朝人比较喜欢穿的那种挂子,然后配马裤,就是比较宽松的裤子。
所以我在做完内层之后呢,我就会给它加一个梭绿,让它贴紧我们的模特儿。
然后给它穿一条套在外面的裤子。
这当然不是所有人都要做中国风的。
我不是操作速度很快,是因为这是我事先录好的视频。
挂子,对,挂。
然后我就会给它做一个腰带。
因为这个衣服是在里面的,是看不到的,这个裤子。
它会被遮住,所以我就做的比较随意了,这个心态。
我本人的操作速度是不可能这么快的。
然后做完腰带之后呢,我会给它应用一个粘衬。
应用粘衬之后,这个腰带就会维持原来的一个形态了。
接下去就是会对这个裤子的长短进行一个调整。
然后比较长的地方我就会放一个裤子。
那个地方我就会把它切掉。
不是,我不是一边做一边直播的。
然后就是把这个裤子稍微拉宽一点。
因为古代的穿的裤子它们都是上面比较宽松,然后下面是塞到靴子里面的。
然后我会把裤子的侧边的曲线调整一下。
因为原来的它太拱了。
嗯。
现在人穿的裤子线条不会像我们现在的线条那么明显。
然后也是一样给它加一些缩滤。
加缩滤之后,下方加一些固定针。
然后这个裤子就会有那种穿的塞到靴子里的感觉。
然后再把上面的这个缩滤给放掉。
给它应用一个面料。
这里我一开始尝试的是亚麻面料。
哈哈哈。
接下去呢,我会截一个它的脚的一个侧面图作为一个参考,然后来画靴子。
当然,这次比赛过程中,只有服装的创建是规定一定要在Marvelous Designer里面创建的。
像靴子啊,还有帽子这种配件,你是可以在其他3D软件里面做的。
我这里只是给大家演示一下。
如果你想在MD里面做靴子的话,是怎么样的一个操作。
然后就画两个鞋子板片。
画完之后,调整一下它们的位置。
还有画脚底的板片。
然后我这里翻来翻去,我都没有搞懂,哎,到底应该怎么翻。
最后我实在忍不住了,我就用那个定位球去翻它们了。
然后就把,就是这个鞋底的板片和侧面的板片翻出来。
然后在做鞋子的时候呢,想跟大家讲一下,就是因为我们的模特的脚底是贴着地板的。
There are no prizes in the competition, but there are prizes
There are very very expensive cards
There will also be MD's permanent permit
Then I started to adjust, to continuously adjust his shoes
Because there are some boards, the previous board was too small
He will wrap the model's legs very strange, and there will be conflicts
Then I went little by little to enlarge this board
Then apply the leather fabric to it, let it stand up
Then I was checking if my footboard board was a little too small
You can see the little crab
Yes, RTL
2080Ti
I don't remember who it seems to be
Then go home
I want to see what I'm going to do at home
Then I changed a fabric for him
Because the leather fabric is too hard
It's not easy to fold
I changed the fabric for him
Yes
On my YouTube channel, I usually divide the video into two groups
First group is the normal live use
The content that everyone will see
There is also one is my whole operation process video
If you think it's too fast
If you can go PR and check the original video
Then the speed of playing this video is a little slower
You know what I did
MD is a Korean software, but we have a branch in China, and basically we will reply to the Korean headquarters for all the opinions you have given us.
It looks like a pair of socks. It looks like a pair of shoes when you sit on it.
Oh, it's stuck. Did I touch it?
Oh, maybe when I sat on it for half of the time, my brain was stuck.
Maybe I went to eat a piece of cookie.
And then...
There's no way in the middle.
And then I'm going to adjust the shape of this shoe.
And then I sat down and I felt like the soles of my feet were a little big.
And then I'm going to adjust its position.
And then I use this fabric on the front.
The bottom of the shoe is a leather fabric.
The original speed video is after I upload the live broadcast.
I will divide it into two pages.
The first one is on P1 and P2.
If you think this speed is too fast, you can watch P2.
There is a pure audio version.
I named it the pure audio version because it doesn't have my voice.
It's just a video of pure operation.
Just follow the video and do it.
Oh, it's like this.
And then I'm going to adjust its shape little by little.
It's still going to fix its curve.
I'm going to drag it around.
And then when I'm done, I'm going to see that there are some cracks on the other boards.
I'm going to adjust it a little bit.
Let's simulate it together.
After the simulation, I cut a board for it.
As a...
It's...
It's like I'm looking at a reference picture.
There's a line in front of me.
And then I made a line in that line.
And then the pure audio version of the video will have background music.
But the sound is very light.
If you want to listen to it, you can turn it up.
I didn't want to add music.
But if I don't add music, BBB won't play it for me.
So I can only add it.
And then I always see this board coming out of it.
So then I applied a layer to this shoe board.
Because if you want to make shoes in MD, you have to keep adjusting it.
So in this game, you can carve shoes in ZB.
It's just clothes.
Clothes.
This kind of thing.
It's a rule that must be done in MD.
Because in the end, you need to upload a front view and a back view.
There's also a screenshot of a 2D version.
And then we'll...
I was thinking about what the pants of the ancient people were like.
And then I thought about it for half a day.
I found that...
It seems to be a little bigger along the waist.
And then everyone finally submitted the work.
The posture can be changed.
Because I used this model directly at the time.
I didn't change his posture.
If you can do some adjustments to his posture in other software, it's okay.
And then I'll emphasize it again.
In the process of making clothes.
To make clothes more stable.
You can do it in the process.
In the process, reduce the particle diameter.
Instead of reducing it together at the end.
Just do it while you're doing it.
To reduce its particle diameter.
And then freeze those.
Unusable version.
Where to sign up?
On our official website.
All you have to do is make your own work.
It's these three pictures.
Just post it.
Just upload it.
There's an activity page on the official website.
We click on the official website.
Pigeon.
Pigeon is not the hardest material to design.
Pigeon is the hardest material to design.
But Pigeon.
I can't say it's the hardest.
It's just not easy to bend.
It's not easy to fold.
You change all the physical properties to 99.
It's the hardest fabric.
It's the hardest fabric you can buy.
Then I setting its value.
To make sure.
That our model has no problems.
Then I touching the fabric.
To make sure.
That our model has no problems.
Then I touching the fabric.
To make sure.
That our model has no problems.
That our model has no issues.
Then push the button.
And then turn over.
and then reduce it to 100
and then the top layer of the clothes will be worn out
A lot of people don't know about this method
You just increase the number of layers
Then I will adjust some of its shapes
After the clothes are worn out
you can reduce the number of layers to 100
and it will be worn out again
Then I will adjust the waistline of the outer layer
Here you can see I am drawing the inner line
Actually I am thinking about the neckline of the chest
the traditional Chinese neckline
How to make the neckline
I didn't think about how to make it
so I will use the pattern to replace the neckline
I am going to make it at the end
and I don't care about it
Then I will use the fabric for the neckline
I was going to add an OBJ on top of the fabric
but I didn't care about it
Then I am going to add an OBJ on top of the fabric
I think it was too short
so I am going to make it longer
Remember to adjust the seam line
If you want me to change the size of the pants
then don't do it
It's not necessary
Then I am going to reduce the size of the pants
I am going to change the size from 60% to 90%
Then I am going to check the shape of the pants
I think the pants are still too short
So I am going to adjust the length of the pants
I am going to expand the length of the pants
The last thing I am going to do is a bird's nest
I am not a bird's nest
Because my mother has a bird's nest in her name
So I really like the bird's nest
So I made her a bird's nest
After I made it, I showed it to my mother
My mother said
How can there be an ancient man
using such a complicated button
This is too ugly
At that time, I felt like I was cracked
I was very angry
I told my mother that this was a bird's nest
Do you understand?
Then my mother said
Oh, that's fine
Then I made another layer
It's the same way
I adjusted the size of the bird's nest to a relatively large bird's nest
Then apply a layer to it
Yes, it's a bit like the clothes of Da Taiji
Mainly because I was watching the MV of Huo Yuanjia
I have been wondering what his clothes were like
Actually, it was hard for me to imagine
What kind of hunter would shoot in that era?
In China...
I went to search for Chinese hunters
When did they have it?
They told me
There was a Han Dynasty or something
And they were shooting arrows
I was like, no way
We're going to use that handgun now
The bird's nest is like a bird's nest
You'll see it later
Then I started to prepare the belt for her
The belt is to make a very wide and long version
Then arrange it around the model
Look at the shape after arranging
Adjust the shoulder
I re-enacted the pants and inner layers
Because it can speed up the computer operation a little bit faster
Re-enacted version
Oh, it's like this
I know that the gun was made in China
But there was a period in the middle
Because it stipulates
Our theme this time is
Hunters' clothes from 1800 to 1900
At that time, it was still more popular to use bows in China
Because it's a coincidence or not
It was the Han Dynasty
I remember it was like
The era when the fighting was more intense
Then there were more hunting
It's all with bows
Yes, I made more layers of clothes
Then you will see here
I added a lot of fixed needles
I basically added a lot of fixed needles
Let it tighten everywhere
After tightening
I will put the middle positioning
Those fixed needles are gradually deleted
Then pull the two ends
These fixed needles
Let this plate shrink up
There is also the original belt
Its one
Shorter
I applied a shrink to it
Let it be a comparison now
In fact, it is shorter than the actual belt
A plate that needs to be cut
You can see that I will have a comparison
Then put this plate
Its friction coefficient is adjusted high
The friction coefficient of the material must be adjusted high
This can effectively prevent
The knot you hit
Disappear in the later simulation process
It doesn't matter
As long as you reduce the particle diameter first
Then
Because the thickness itself
It's just a visual thickness
Conflict thickness
Because the original conflict thickness is 3
The original conflict thickness is 2.5
In fact, it's okay
Then you can see
It used to be
There is a shrink in it
Because I have two sides
Double machine on both sides
This line
Each created two rows of fixed needles
So this
When you put the shrink back
It will naturally form this
Folding wrinkle
There is a way to form a wrinkle like this
It's better
You don't have to use your hands to stack it anymore
Then you can see that
In the end, you delete these two layers
And then re-multiply
This is the effect of that kind of pile up
It's in the fabric
Wait a minute
Because this process may be faster
The knot is actually good if you play more
It's really good to have a lot of stitches
First of all, you can see that I use the green band to make it into a relatively narrow band
Belt band
Then, I will drag this fixed stitch little by little
The most important thing is that you must add a lot of fixed stitches
You have to make the circle very wide
The circle in the middle
I'll get to that step later
It's really good to have a lot of stitches
It's really a coincidence
Then you can see that I will keep dragging this board
Let him in the middle of this circle
Just keep adding fixed stitches
Just use a fixed stitch to make it into a circle
Then drag this fixed stitch on both ends
You must add a lot of fixed stitches during the process
Then you can see that I have a lot of stitches
Actually, I actually do this
It won't take long to wear a belt
It's pretty fast
Then you must pay attention when you pull
This board is stable
Don't make it too stretched
Then when he is more stable
The friction coefficient can be seen as the fabric
Choose a kind of fabric
The fabric of this belt version
Then raise its friction coefficient
This can prevent this knot from spreading
Is the friction coefficient in the fabric and physical properties
If this section looks like it's still
If you don't understand
You can take a look at the pure box version
You can slow down the playback speed a little bit
Then here is the top and bottom
Use a fixed stitch
Add two rows of fixed stitches
Then put the friction coefficient from just 60
Put back 100
Then the part of the middle that is more out
It will stack together by itself
Is to do this kind of folding love
A method of folding
Long-sleeved belt
But my belt is long-sleeved now
Fold 5 times
The front and back, the back and sides
Because of the MD
It is indeed a little trouble to adjust it by hand
If it is a vanity, even if there is such a movement
It may be more difficult to deal with
Because you may find all kinds of problems in the middle
I still can not understand the square body of the belt
Then I drew one
This is actually a sketch of a crossbody bag
Actually, if you take a look at the video, I think I did it very quickly
Actually, I also went to search for the bag that looks like a beggar's cup
I searched for a long time, but I couldn't find it
So I had to draw it myself
Oh, the rectangle, I understand
The rectangle is very difficult to draw
If you want to have thickness, you can just add the thickness of the rectangle
I'm not going to make a rectangle out of the software
You can just add the thickness of the rectangle
It's also very hard for me to imagine how to make a rectangle
So I just copied a layer of cologne to make a bag
I originally wanted to add some creases to the side
And then the inside of the cologne will turn over the surface
So that the two sides of the bag are facing out
The original intention is not to help the helpers
I just thought about it
What kind of feeling do hunters have?
Because you are wearing clothes that look like people who play Tai Chi
This kind of one
If you participate in the competition, it will look more
More fashionable
There are few details
So I just want to make it for him
A cloth bag like this
Welcome
All right
Do I have to match high heels with him?
This has become a female boss
Uh, the thickness performance
First of all, when you do it in MD
You have to increase the conflict thickness a little bit
Then you put this
Thickness of blood
Just a little bit more out
It's good
The reason I can think of is that maybe you are wearing thickness
If so
Then you don't wear thickness
Just pour it out
Then such a cloth bag
In fact, there are mainly these wrinkles now
It's because I changed its fabric to a silk fabric
Silk fabric itself is more likely to have wrinkles
It's easy to have wrinkles
Then I added a sleeve for him
After that, I was ready to make him a shoe strap
Because I was doing it at the time
I think
How to do it
The more you look at it, the more you look like a beggar
I feel like a beggar should not be able to afford a gun
So I just want to give him
Let's make a belt for the gun
Look at the leather bag
I don't give you a leather bag
The main thing is that I was
On the reference picture he gave me
I look at the bag
It has a metal buckle
Then I was thinking
Is there such a thing as a metal buckle in China in 1800?
It doesn't seem to be
Then I didn't make it for him
I just thought it was enough to make him a puff bag
Hi
Don't remind me of the bow
Then this is the fabric of the belt
Change to leather fabric
Then I copied another layer out
The problem with the thickness of the CB
It seems to be said before
Is it related to the hair line?
I remember
Specifically
You can go to the group and send a screenshot
Because I may not be able to understand your question very well now
The bottom left corner is our new QQ group
A number and a password
You can go to the group
Communicate about the problems you usually encounter
Other standards are
This is a small bag
I also made that small bag
Just
I will show you later
How to make that small bag
In this way, I will adjust its size
It is very important when changing Chinese clothing
There is also
In fact, this time
This time Crytek and Marvelous Designer
This game of cooperation
There is no rule that you must use
Your local clothing
So it is
If you want to make Western clothes
It's okay
It's just that I received
The task is to do Chinese
So I just made a Chinese one
Why did you start to discuss the help of Crytek?
I didn't want to be the help of Crytek
So I actually
Usually encounter this kind of work
Related to guns
And then I just
Do it by my own imagination
Then I will do the one next to it
The bag hanging
Just create a relatively small version first
The particle diameter of this version must be reduced first
Otherwise, because this version is too small
The grid on it is very small
It's hard to get through this
Slant bag
Then it's the same
Add a fixed pin
Drag the fixed pin around this bag
Really
Are there already more than 20 people in the group?
Pretty good
You can usually be in the group
More and more atmosphere
Then I am now
At that time I was thinking
Why can't I always choose this fixed pin?
I was angry
Why can't I choose it?
So annoying
I was angry at that time
Then I
I'm angry now
I've been fighting with him for a long time
Just very angry
I'm all
I just
At that time I just
I tried many times
Then I decided to report the bug
Just this
Then they told me this bug
Just now often have
So everyone is in the process
Add a fixed pin
If you can't add it
Or if you can't choose it
Just add it again
Now
Don't add now
It's good to have MD
If you add it now
There's no hint
Are you really going to add now?
Use Stephane.
Is that right?
The group number is at the lower left corner
On my head
There is our group number
Because it's a new group
So I can't memorize the group number
Everyone just
I'll just input it manually. Thank you everyone.
Then I'll take two ropes
and put them on. Actually, I put one layer on
and then put another layer on.
Then I'll start making the front bag.
First, I'll make a round-shaped plate.
Then I'll reduce its particle diameter to 15.
Then I'll double-click its plate outline.
I can create a fixed point along its outline.
Then I'll draw the internal line diameter.
I'll draw a circle on the internal line.
Then I'll apply a folding angle to it.
Let it fold.
Then I'll add a fixed point.
Then I'll apply a elasticity to the inner circle.
Then it'll become a small bag.
Isn't it amazing?
Oh! MD9!
Oh no, I accidentally leaked it.
MD9 is not MD10.
9.5, 9.5.
10 is...
It's developing now.
I'm sorry.
9.5.
Then I'll reduce the particle diameter.
Then I'll draw the elasticity in the middle.
It's a front bag.
Isn't it amazing?
It's a completely new experience.
I didn't expect it.
A front bag is so convenient.
I even printed it.
Good, good.
10 is coming soon.
It should be October or November.
Because the impact of the epidemic may be in November.
Now there are some new features in development.
But I can't ask.
Because we can't tell you what new features we have now.
I can tell you secretly.
There will be a new model in the future.
And the style is different from everyone else.
It's a very cute model.
But I can't tell you what the model looks like.
It's a newly developed model of MD.
Maybe next time we'll be able to see this new model of MMD.
I can't say it again.
It's okay to say it again.
Just add a fixed needle first.
Then fold it.
Actually, the main reason I folded it
is because I wanted to see how to shrink this bag.
Then add the elasticity to the inner loop.
It's a very simple step.
Draw a circle.
Then draw a loop in the middle.
Draw a line directly with the inner loop.
Then draw a line.
Then add the elasticity on the line.
Then you can make a bag yourself.
ZB is stealing MD's business.
MD should also be stealing ZB's business.
It's not me.
I'm a fat girl.
That girl is very cute.
She has a different style from me.
She also has a different hairstyle.
Although I don't know if she's really on the market.
It's not on the market.
It's just added to our model of MD.
Will she be able to change her hairstyle?
But as far as I know, she has a double horse tail.
And ZB is not stealing our business.
I had a friend ask me before.
Hey, is this ZB now?
Are you working on fabric development?
Some new functions for fabric disassembly.
I said, yes, yes.
Then someone else said,
Your company needs to work harder.
ZB is going to surpass you.
I said, yes, yes.
I will work hard.
I'll develop it again.
Then the next step is to untie the other panels.
And then together.
Let's simulate it together.
Actually, it's almost the same at the end.
I think it's almost the same here.
Then I just want to say.
It seems that people who watch them play Tai Chi
will turn their sleeves over.
Then I just turned his sleeves over.
Fabric brush.
I can only say this function.
CBO.
And then Marvelous Designer.
I can't say too much.
You just have to experience it yourself.
Then use the folding tool.
Use the folding arrangement tool.
You can fold the sleeves right here.
To simulate.
Then the other side.
I'll delete the original version.
Then directly control D.
A layer of cologne.
Go to the side.
Oh, it's not Bilibili.
We didn't cooperate with Bilibili.
We sang it ourselves.
Then it's a very magical part.
You can see that I cut out an MD.
Just draw an internal line there.
Then sew up a small strip.
The main reason is that
I prefer to try everything in MD.
Then add the thickness of it.
Add the thickness of the rendering.
It becomes something like a plate buckle.
No.
I didn't say.
You can't.
I don't know.
I didn't say.
This is because I can't say.
I don't know either.
I don't know if it's true.
Then the plate buckle is done.
When I put it in like this,
I found that this plate buckle seems a little big.
Then I will use the folding tool.
Make it a little bit of a shape on the ground.
How to do it.
If you want to see it,
Show it to everyone again.
Just draw the internal line first.
Then look at how long it is.
Draw a rectangular rectangle.
Sew it up.
Then reduce the particle diameter.
Then it's done.
Isn't it amazing?
MD connection engine interface.
In fact,
Our previous one.
Like Senza.
His second life.
Is connected to our software.
That engine.
Like their software.
The clothes in MD.
When the clothes are disassembled.
It's in their.
It's okay inside.
About the engine connection.
This thing.
Just.
I can only say.
Let it go.
It's still on the way.
How to make it thicker.
Just put it.
Surge.
Surge thickness.
Increase.
Then.
Remember to open.
The 3d window.
The thick texture.
The surface.
To see the thick version.
Then.
The new one.
This copy.
It's weight.
From.
From ten thousand grams.
To zero.
After I.
I put in.
After the copy.
I suddenly realized.
It seems that.
I don't need those.
Rectangle.
The.
And then I deleted all of those
Okay, so I've actually completed all of the final steps
And this is the picture I showed at the end
In the middle, I just had to go through a little bit of text processing
And it became the final product
I feel like the people who are entering the live stream right now
It's already very late and they can only look at this picture
Okay, so this is the final result that I've made
When you guys are participating in this competition
It's already okay to have made this kind of result
I mainly want you guys to remember to show off
Don't bring a bag
I was just saying that I wanted to share some other tips with you guys
So I added all of these bags in
Because in the process that you guys are doing
You guys might not have thought about
Making a bag like this
And making a belt like this
Clothes buttons
You can wait until our video is uploaded
And then you can go and take a look
We will have a live stream that no one is talking about
By then, I can use chats to show you guys
For example, making clothes buttons
Where are the clothes buttons
Where are the buttons
And then you can take a look at that video
The pattern on the top is a sticker
Wait a minute
Let me show you guys this picture
Where is my picture
Blackboard
I'm just...
Just because Fangji has blackboard
So I won't participate in the competition
Um, for your culture, you can do it in MD
I do it in my culture in PS
And then you can import the stickers
Let's see, my project file is here
This is my last completed project file
In fact, these are just some stickers
which are the stickers that I added
including these blood marks
I drew them all directly in the PS
MD thickness
when you draw out the thickness
because I'm not too sure
I remember that a lot of my friends
would draw it thin in the CV
and then make it thicker
Does the dungeon have a personal BZ number?
Actually it does
but my personal BZ number
is a game
I play games
so I don't have
anything to do with MD
on top of that
You can't show up in MD
I showed up in another V-Ray
and then
in this competition
as long as you don't use
the game engine
you can't use other game engines
you can only use CryEngine
this game engine
other game engines
such as V-Ray
and other game engines
can be used
I used V-Ray
and then
like this one
I just simply
added some stickers
I added its texture
and then
these are all simple
some cherry blossoms
and some traces of snow
actually this snow
my colleague told me
when the snow is finished
it feels like it's from a
rich young man's song
to a poor young man's song
and then
originally I didn't have this kind of snow
I added some dust
he told me
it looks ugly
and then I felt very wronged
so I changed the color
and then I changed it to snow
the thickness of the button
is something that you can
drag out by itself
when you drag it out
remember to drag out
the obj form
after the button
my button
is when you are
dragging the md
obj file
for example
if you choose this button
and then the file
when you drag out the obj
you can choose its thickness
thickness and thickness
as long as you drag out the thick one
it will be fine
what is the name of the peace elite
that's right
I don't play peace elite
how much thickness does it have
md actually has
I don't understand
why don't people
like to use
the thickness of the snow
you choose this
for example
now I have a board
and then
I will increase the thickness of the snow
to 3
and then there is a little card
it is a thick board
yes
add to the middle
to make a hunter
why do I add a money bag
because I feel that hunters
should all have a certain
feeling of reward
so
I must have something
that can hold money
so I made him a money bag
it is actually thick
if you don't
want this kind of bending effect
you can turn off the bending
rate
md how to make a uv picture
first md
in the upper right corner
there is a uv editor
in the uv editor
you can
make a simple
adjustment to the uv picture
what's wrong with my uv editor
maybe because of the picture
there are too many pictures
put the uv to the 2d version
position
put the uv to 1.2
confirm
oh
ok
after you export this
the file
export obj or fdx
when you export
you can choose
a unified uv picture
I won't type
ok
Wang Zhileong
I type
Heroes Alliance
and
some card games
and some card games
yes
at the end
I thought
other details
are not very similar to
Hunter
so I made it
different
to make it
more
like
it feels
I feel like it's more like the characteristics of China
Because when you talk about the characteristics of China, they all have a very deep impression on people
For example, the Jiang Shi of the Qing Dynasty, and so on
But for us, people who do magic, they will probably wear a painting
So I added it to it
Eh, what was I talking about just now?
There is a unified UV coordinate when you pour OBJ
If you can choose this, you can pour the UV drawing out
No, I'm in Zu'an
Oh, I know
Yes, the bag
These lines are for adding thickness
MD clothes, how thick are they?
Game process
It's a lot of work to add thickness, right?
So a lot of times, when I pour it out, I like to pour the bag out
No
It's okay
Then everyone must participate, remember to participate a lot
As far as I know, there is not much yet
There are not many people who are doing some投稿
Of course, it does not rule out that everyone likes to do some投稿 on the afternoon of September 16th, the last day
Because uploading pictures is very simple
As long as you upload the front picture of Xuanran
Front picture, back picture, and for example, everyone just puts it in one compression bag
A picture of this 2D version
I actually put the 3D version together
It will be more convenient to see
There are also back pictures and front pictures
Just three pictures
The standard we refer to is actually these three pictures
OK
Why is the added display thickness
Pour out OBJ is thick
If you choose thick, it will
Pour out according to your display thickness
Then if you pour thin
It is based on its center
This thin version is poured out
The lower left corner is the newly created
I have a QQ group number and password on my lower left corner
We will make some changes to this password indefinitely
So remember to pay attention to some of our movements at any time
We will tell you the password of the new issue
Because this group is still expanding gradually
Little friends can add groups
Xuanran picture is not only using A pose
Xuanran picture is possible
Any pose is possible
As long as this model is you from CryEngine
The model of Crytek that came down
Can I not use text?
No, you can't
You must add text
You can not add text
But it is
Is the judge
Will consider
Then text material
You can produce it with other software
Not that you can only fill in the picture on the PS
You can use other text software
There is also Xuanran software
There is a specific way to compete
On our official website
There will be some tips here
Is the FAQ
And the official website
He will have one
Is the page of the introduction
See more
This will also have
Substance Painter can be
It's okay
OK
Can be used
The latest
Tutorial video
Are you preparing
But
Because it's more English
So we
In
Those videos
There may be some translation
And so on
What is the ratio of other software?
You mean
In the whole production process
The ratio of other software?
Except for clothes
All
Including
Shoes
Hats
This kind
You can do it in other software
Just say
Your clothes
It is
Our common knowledge
Clothes
Is to be in
In Marvelous Designer
Do
You can not use your own model
Can not
Can
You can
You can use other software
For example
You can use the
Other software
The ratio of other software
Is
As long as the clothes are made in MD
Because we will look at
Your
2D version of the window
The version of these clothes in it
Other
Gloves
Shoes
We don't force you to do it in Marvelous Designer
I'll show you
Just say
In the process of production
If you want to challenge yourself
In Marvelous Designer
It's okay to make shoes
Can you use the official model of the second season?
No
You must use Crytek
This game
In the asset pack
Virtual model
Among them, there are male models, female models and
A doll
It seems to be
All can be used
So be sure to remember to go to CryEngine
Put the material bag down
Can
If you want to upload other more details
It can be
But remember to upload
This compression bag must not exceed 50MB
Just can't exceed 50MB
You can have some other details
Add
Add details to the picture
This one
We are all OK
Just remember the total compression bag
Don't exceed 50MB
Then the end time of this game is
September 16th
That is, the time of the resolution is
Before 4 o'clock in the afternoon on September 16th
Is 3.59
such
The website of the model is to Crytek
To download on their website
Wait a minute
In our Q&A
The FAQ
There is the overall tutorial on the page
Time is short
Because
The game started at the beginning of August
Now there is one month left
Everyone is
So if you are a professional, you can join the professional group
And if you are more professional, for example if you are a student
You can join the professional group, that's ok
Of course, don't go to the professional group all the time
You'll get scammed, just don't
There are some here
Just click here, and you'll jump to the CryEngine Marketplace
And here you can log in, register to log in
I'm just getting ready to start learning today
I'll try my best
It's ok
We welcome everyone to send us all kinds of posts
Of course, don't force yourself to send it
Remember to go to the official page
And upload it there
And when you upload it
Remember not to cover it
Because we judge your standards
It's the most recent upload of the compression bag
So remember not to upload it wrong
Three years have passed
What song is that?
How can I know if I'm old or not?
Think about it
You can go to the professional group
If you're a comma
And then for example school student
Or someone who doesn't have lots of skills
You can go to the professional group
And remember to this
Do it
Remember the rendering
Did I use Liray to choose the last one?
Re-enroll today's course and then apply for it?
Don't you think so?
Everyone is the same after all
MD's official reviewer is my boss
Yes, so if you do the same thing as me, she will find out
And it's actually really good to make clothes alone
Everyone uses their usual weekend time to do it, it must be in time
I saw Mia donkey
Is that the thorn of Mingyufangzhou?
It looks good, of course it will add points
It can also be changed to a girl's version
Just remember that the whole thing must be in line with the era of Crytek
It must be from 1800 to a certain year
That is, the clothing that came out in the 1920s
Just don't be too modern and don't be too ancient
How can I work at an MD company?
You can send me a resume
My email is shenry at marvelousdesigner.com
You can send your resume
If there is an English version, just send the English version
If the English version is not that good, you can send the Chinese version
It's a bit difficult
That era
The fashion reference of the era
There are very few
You can refer to the historical literature written on it
So actually, if you don't think Chinese is so easy to do
You can do Western style
It's not that we set the style for everyone
It must be something
As long as the style and the effect you want to present are unified
As long as we think it's OK
It's not that you have to be a Chinese in the Chinese region
In that case, it will limit your thinking too much
I just because
My task is to be a Chinese
So I chose to be a Chinese
You can be a Chinese
If you are good at doing Western style, you can do it
Shenryu boss, man or girl
Being a man and a woman are almost the same
They are all OK
If you have enough time, you can do both
It's just that doing both is still doing one
It doesn't make a difference to us
No plus or minus
Overall
主要还是看你的一个风格,还有你做的一个,哪一些用的,就是整体的美感这样。
怎么在内部线上加一圈细圆柱?
你就缝一个长方形的板片上去就好了。
不要,不是说老大是韩国人你们就做韩式的。
如果我们老大是韩国人的话,那我们作为中国的小伙伴肯定是不太熟悉韩国当时一个风格的。
所以只要做自己比较喜欢的风格就可以了,没有必要去投其所好的。
因为不是说评委只有我们老大一个人,评委其实是由世界各地的好多个评审一起组成的。
。
没有加分像男人什么时候站起来,男的女的都一样了。
你用男模特女模特都一样,然后你用两个模特也不会比一个模特要好。
这是大家只要尽力去做就行了。
一个模特和两个模特在我们评审分的过程中是没有区别的。
不会因为你多做一个就多给你一点分,然后你少做一个就少给你一点分,不是这样的。
。
And currently, because we haven't talked about everyone's resume yet, let's talk about the recruitment thing later.
If you really really really really want to come to MD, we are also more welcome to come to our company with the same resume at any time.
The main thing is for those who are more interested in MD, models can be changed to black and white.
You mentioned a very magical point, it should be okay, right?
If it's not okay, you can add a group first, and then you can add me and ask me later.
I can ask my colleagues later.
Thank you.
Do you have any other questions?
Or any comments about MD?
You can ask them during our live stream.
On the bottom left corner, there is our official group.
And there is also a password added to the official group.
You can enter the password directly into our group.
Actually, the original password was the other way around.
The original password was the other way around.
It's the other one.
And then,
and then,
I changed the password afterwards.
Press the blackboard.
Do models have to have two hands? Can't the disabled be recognized?
I can ask you. You can add me first.
I promise I won't hit you.
I can ask you.
Can you stand up?
We can.
It's just that...
Lovers...
Hands...
Lovers with two hands might be a little more flexible.
After you asked me this question, I became dumbfounded.
Hmm...
Maybe you're just like in the TV series.
You put the model's hand into the clothes,
and then pretend that he has two hands.
And then pretend that he has two hands.
I really didn't think about it.
Can I only have one hand?
Their models should not be changed.
You can change your posture, but you can't make him a hunter with one hand.
A hunter with one hand?
He changed his bullet. How?
How can he change his bullet?
Hunters must be people.
Don't use that picture.
I saw a very funny picture today.
I can't take it out.
It's about formism.
自由主义,纯粹不纯粹的那个九张图,赛博朋克的,然后左上角就是形式纯粹,然后什么什么纯粹的话就是公巧机动队,然后右下角那个我记得很清楚是小马宝丽,小马宝丽也是赛博朋克中的一种。
不是吧,阿森,怎么就开始讨论起单只手的猎人了。
多个2D版面的缩放啊。
嗯,你指的是选这种版片之后的缩放吗,还是其他的一些什么内容,嗯,就是。
习惯用Maya到MD就很难操作。
你是说多个?
多个镜头吗?就是正视图,侧视图,我有点不是很好理解。
线段卡缝到模特身体怎么编辑,用编辑工具直接去拖动那些点就可以去编辑。
哦,我知道了。
我习惯用MayaCB的操作方式的话,你就直接到MD里面,嗯,换一个操作方式就好了。
你们不要再想这一些奇怪的模特了。
我感觉把模特弄断一只手已经很离谱了。
哎,我这样都卡住了脑袋。
这里有Maya的操作方式。
如果你说的是多个版片缩放,嗯,CryEngine你下载好慢的话,嗯,我们只能说,很脏。
嗯,对,我是比较喜欢就是稍微有一点点脏的感觉的,所以我给它做了一些雪啊,灰尘啊之类的。
嗯,我觉得你为了符合他们CryEngine的那个猎杀对决这个游戏风格的话,嗯,还是脏一点比较正常。
就是,毕竟那个年代做猎人的应该都不太厉害吧。
对哦,1800年的猎人哪有装火箭什么联动器的,没有的。
可以的。
嗯。
这是不是有纸和布料之间有距离啊。
你可以自己倒一个钮扣进来。
一定要做猎人。
不能做老师,也不能做模特,只能做猎人。
耶。
ummy Beloved-
荒野大飄客 荒野大飄客 荒野大飄客 荒野大飄客的話 它沒有定死那個年代吧
我記得是有線的長度可以選的 線的長度
線的長度選可不可以出復的 好像可以
如果你覺得它離得太遠的話 你就把線的長度改成負數就可以了
試圖操作很困難 選中之後直接放大放小啦 這樣很困難嗎
是因為覺得它看上去就是不是以中心為基準是不是
如果是這樣的話 雙擊中間這個點就會變成中心點
你是不是比較喜歡這樣的說法
真的啊
哎呀 那可能是我對美國的這個不了解
我最近還看了個漢密爾頓那個音樂劇
也是講美國就比較之前的那一些故事
音樂劇還挺好看
你是不是要這樣的說法啊
就是之前的說法看上去比較不方便的話
你可以用這個 這個功能
雙擊中間的這個點就會呼出中心點 然後進行縮放
清朝皇室打獵的也可以做的
只是當時我其實有想過做那一些朝廷命官的風格
但是我發現他們都是比較喜歡射箭的
當時還是因為年代的問題比較喜歡用一些射箭的
射箭的話呢
就和我們現在說的這一些火炬是有一點不一樣的
當然它也有那種火槍也是可以做的
對哦 我們好像古代是有那種火槍
就是不是想像中的那種散彈槍啊
還有步槍這種
哦 二地窗口縮放啊
可是換成Maya的也不方便啊
它是根據你鼠標指的位置進行縮放的
哦 你是想直接以中心為縮放是不是啊
那你可以按住 Alt 鍵
然後鼠標左鍵拉
就是以中心縮放
哦 那我學習到了
對哦 突然想起來有火槍
那做清朝的皇室的也是可以的
只是我當時腦補了一下
獵殺對決平時遇到的那一些怪物
它的風格
我還是做選了做了就是沒那麼
那麼中式的
其實大家做一些就是皇帝啊什麼命官啊
包括一些帶軍甲的
我覺得都可以吧
但是盔甲這個
就比較曖昧一點這個話題
就我感覺還是布料比較多
然後盡量避免去用一些盔甲的
會好一點
我現在聲音都講啞了
大家還有一些什麼其他的問題
大家有什麼問題
大家有什麼問題嗎
用弩也可以的
總之就是大家
只要自己的風格夠統一化
然後多多參與這次比賽都OK的
因為業餘組真的
大家就是真的可以
試一下各種各樣的
反正你也不吃虧嘛
對我們是在上海的
試圖中居中顯示
你是說選中這個版片之後
我們有一個對焦制選定的
這個嗎
對焦制選定的
然後你按 alt 鍵就是以它為中心
按 alt 鍵就是以它為中心
然後按 alt 鍵就是以它為中心
來贊助 Altafilm
或是按 alt 鍵 Final
然後讓你去放大縮小 fede
cactus
也算不算
美 elk
i
你如果要選中一般
assigning strawberry
左键对焦置选定的,然后按鼠标, Alt键左键,这样就行。
拿弹弓官方,我不知道诶。
因为本身也没有说要做武器。
拿弹弓这个小伙伴,你真的太平了。
我都怀疑是不是我认识的几个朋友里面,哪个人反串过来。
不是吧,不是真的会有微博好友来直播间爆破我的吧。
可以示范一下怎么做拉链吗。
拉链啊,删掉不需要的缝线。
再左右移动就按住鼠标,中键移动就可以了。
然后开启模拟一下。
哦,这个扭扣。
用拉链工具,先选择一个起点,单击一下,然后双击一下,就是第一半边。
然后再选择这个起点,双击一下蓝点。
这个其实叫包边啦。
然后开启模拟,就是一个拉链了,非常时髦的穿法。
然后就可以在不开启模拟的情况下,拖动这个拉链头。
哦,它就是一个很时髦的拉链了。
当然拉链你没有办法改拉链的长段,所以你只能把它直接删除,然后重新去创一个。
如果你要改它的一个拉链的长度的话。
嗯,太客气了。
拉链能导收BJ吗?
可以。
收边功能其实没什么用。
嗯,就不是说大家想象中的收边功能。
它其实更像是一种一圈包边。
点一下,然后双击一下,这样就会有一圈包边。
有一些衣服啊,或者说包包,它会有这样一圈包边在外面。
solidify和strengthen。
呃,strengthen它的中文是硬化。
当你开启硬化的时候,这个版面会变得很硬。
它的褶皱会消失。
比如说你可以看一下啊。
这一硬化,它褶皱是不是消失了。
就感觉它像变成了皮革面料一样的。
但是solidify呢,它的中文叫形态固化。
指的是它现在形成的一些褶皱,会被固定它原来的一个走向。
即使你去拖拽它,它产生一些形变之后,你放手,它还是会维持原来的那个形态。
所以就叫solidify,形态固化。
变形率和变形强度。
他们在我之前有一节讲飞行员的夹克的时候,后半段有提到过这一个区别。
简单来说,控制率指的是,当你一个版片弯曲过后,有百分之多少的版片的面料属性会被缩减。
然后,比如说,就是一个面料它是会弯的嘛。
比如说这个面料,这里弯下来。
然后当一个面料形成褶皱的时候,其实它的形态就已经产生了变化了。
我们这个变形率只不过是百分之多少。
比如说百分之八十,那就是说形成的这个褶皱,可能从这一段往下,它的面料属性都变了。
如果是百分之二十呢,可能就只有从这里往下,它的面料属性变了。
然后变多少呢,是由我们的变形强度来控制的。
或者说变形强度是百分之六十。
那么就从这一段开始往下。
都会变成百分之六十的原本的面料属性。
好,换个问题来看看.
了解我,你们每 기분你都这样,你们可以自己变现的笑情 cracks?
Is it made in other software?
Oh, one is a model...
Not a model, it's a sample of the version
Make it a little smaller
And don't make the clothes too tight
And check if your model has a broken face
Can I not add anything to the franchise? No, you can't
I'll give you two more minutes
You still have two minutes to ask questions
After you ask questions, we can
Uh
The official group
You can add more to our official group
Because the password will be changed at any time
That is to say
Even if you see me in the official video
You may not be able to add the group
Because our group number password will always change
Leave it blank
Think about the design
Yes
Well, you...
You can ask your sewing machine, your sewing machine may know a little more about the details of the ZB sewing machine brush.
One is the name line function in MD, you can add a name line and then make some edits, and then make some modifications to these names.
I am now typing out 66.57 billion light years.
You are just like the one who sells fish, Wang Lei, or the one in Lin Fei, Zhu Zhen Yi.
There are a lot of problems.
You can't, you can't.
Make a scarf yourself, work hard.
There are a lot of MMD streamers on BAB, they will have some knowledge.
In the video we forwarded before, there should be some friends who have made a scarf, you can ask them.
Oh, they are all very thick.
You can increase the strength of the sewing machine a little bit.
It's at the bottom after selecting the fabric.
In the details, increase the bending strength a little bit.
There will be less creases.
Also, your fabric may be too, too much, and creases will form.
How do you make the opening of the sleeve?
There is a tool.
We actually mentioned this just now.
Just use the internal sewing machine first.
Draw an internal line.
Okay.
After drawing an internal line, use the folding, this folding arrangement tool to fold it.
Fold it up, and then open the model.
Eh, it will fold up.
Isn't it amazing?
Folding is one thing, you can check if the model itself has some larger parts.
Also, you can use the scissor to move it around.
Okay.
Then, it seems that we are almost done with the questions now.
2D models.
It's too polite, banana fish, oh, banana fish, two drops of night sky above the seventh seat, the hundred-fold group is not like
Because the whole of it is still the one that's more sharp so after you're done you're going to reduce the particle diameter to five or three
And then delete all the unnecessary lines and then double-click to simulate it
Okay, well, I think it's getting late and you should all go to bed and get some rest and then we're almost done with today's live broadcast
You can't see other people's works that have been submitted online, you can't see them, you can only see them on our backstage
If you want to fold it twice, you can fold it once first and then add a circle to fix it
And then fold it again
Or you can cut this circle down first and then fold the outside side first and then the inside right side
There's a add to the inside and you can use this function
In the pure box, there will be this section of operation that might be faster so you can't see it
well
Then if you want to find me again or if you have any other questions you want to communicate with you can add our lower left corner
Here we have our qq group number and our door password and you can search for our q group number
And then
It's too polite to search for the group number in the lower left corner and enter our door password line
You can join our mb
This one
I'm in the chat group
And then welcome everyone to talk about their own problems at any time and then if I see some problems that I can solve
I'll talk to you in the group
And then I also hope you can participate in our game a lot
And thank you for some of your usual concerns and some of your encouragement and suggestions
Thank you and I'll see you in the next live broadcast
There's a live broadcast, there's a live broadcast today
Bye bye, see you later, bye bye
You're too polite, everyone, thank you, thank you, everyone
Well, we'll see you next time, bye bye, everyone, remember to add our WeChat official account or add our qq group
well
You're too polite, Mo Mo Da, Mo Mo Da, see you later, bye bye, next time, definitely not this time
Thank you, thank you, everyone, see you next time, bye bye
Bye bye
Thank you, everyone, bye bye
Bye, bye
Bye bye
Everyone, goodbye
You're too polite, recognizes
npckie
Hello
Wyvern
Don't open the white box
My content is not my work
手机滑掉了,拜拜,拜拜,大家再见
拜拜
拜拜,拜拜
我的手看不到,拜拜